redshift3d.com 2019-03-26

# Privacy Policy

**At Redshift, we take your privacy seriously.**  
Our principles on privacy are simple:  

  * We only collect and store personal information for the purpose of providing you with a high level of service.
  * We only collect personal information with your consent.
  * We do not and will not sell or share your personal information with anyone.
  * We protect your personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.

This Privacy Policy describes how Redshift Rendering Technologies, Inc. ("Redshift") and its subsidiaries collect and use your personal data.

**Special policy regarding information from children under thirteen**

Redshift's products and the redshitf3d.com website are not tragetted to children under 13 years old. We do not knowingly collect or use any personal information of children 13 years of age without parental consent. In the event that we discover that we have collected such information, we delete it promptly and discontinue any use.

**What kind of information do we collect?**

_Website Use Information:_ Like many websites, we use tools (including Google analytics) to collect anonymous information from visitors in order to better understand how they use our website. We use session cookies to keep you logged in while you use our website. These disappear after you close your browser. We also use persistent cookies which stay in your browser and allow us to recognize you when you return to our website. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can change the settings to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from websites you visit. If you turn off cookies, parts of redshift3d.com may not work for you.

_Personally Identifiable Information:_ If you create an account on redshift3d.com, we ask you to provide your name, email address and a password. We collect and store this information so that we can identify you as a registered user for access to private areas of our website including product downloads, provide you with product activation keys and personalized access to our forums including optional forum email notifications. In addition, you may opt in to receive information and updates about our products and services, in which case we may use your email address to contact you.

_Payment information:_ If you purchase a license of Redshift from our website, we collect your billing and payment information, and any other information necessary to complete the transaction. The only payment information we store are transaction ids and, for credit card payments, the expiration date and last four digits of the credit card used to make the purchase.

_Social networking data:_ Redshift has pages on social networking platforms including Facebook, Twitter and LinkedIn that you may choose to visit and use to communicate with us. When interacting with these pages, a link between your social media platform user account and our pages may be created by the social media platform. Redshift does not have direct influence on the type of data collected in this process. The Redshift social media pages may include buttons, tools, plugins or other content. When you interact with such content, for example by clicking on a "Like", "Follow" or "Share" button, or by writing a comment, content from the Redshift pages may automatically appear in your social media platform profile.

_System Information and Usage Data:_ We collect system information during the license activation of our software product. In addition, our software products may collect system information during normal operation and associate this system information with your redshift3d.com account.

**How do we use your information?**

_To personalize your experience_. Your information helps us respond more effectively to your individual needs.

_To improve our website_. Along with direct feedback from users, the information we collect provides us with valuable insight into our visitors' usage patterns.

_To process transactions_. We never share your information with any outside parties except for the sole purpose of completing transactions for license purchases.

_To keep you in the loop_. When you purchase a license of Redshift, the email address you provide will be used to send you information pertaining to your order, including information on how to download and install Redshift. In addition, you may _opt in_ to receive our newsletter and other company or product news via email.

_For licensing and security purposes_. System information collect during license activation and while operating Redshift software is used to reduce software piracy and fraud, and to prevent unauthorized use of Redshift software.

**Your information, your choice**

Redshift provides you with choices for the the use of your information. You may choose to not share any personal information with Redshift. This choice may affect your ability to use the redshift3d.com website, access trial and other downloads or use the Redshift forums. If you choose to share your email address or other personal information by registering on the redshift3d.com website, you can choose to limit when Redshift communicates with you. 

**Storage and retention of personal information**

We store personal information of users on our servers and servers of companies we hire to provide services to us. Your information may be stored in the United States as well as other countries where Redshift operates and in countries where our hired service provides operate

Your personal information is stored only as long as we need it to honor to fulfill the purposes described in this privacy statement or as required/permited by applicable law and regulations.

**How to contact us?**

If you have privacy questions, concerns or complaints you can contact us by mail or email. 

_By email_  

_By mail_  
Redshift Rendering Technologies, Inc.  
4590 MacArthur Blvd., Suite 500  
Newport Beach, CA 92660  
U.S.A.

_Last updated May 24, 2018_
